# Annika Lundberg

CV



Email: annika.birgitta@hotmail.com

Phone: +46 73 633 20 37

I'm a motivated result-driven 22 year old girl from sweden who loves design and human interaction. I worked with different companies and been engaged in many associations and always put a lot of time and effort in my projects. In the future I dream about working with design while making the world a better place.

# **Experience**

#### **UX-designer/Designer**

Aug 2019 - Present

We Know IT, Linköping, Sweden

- Head of the design in different projects and works directly with programmers and customers
- Designing logos and websites
- Managing different kinds of projects at the same time

## Web designer (internship)

Aug 2018 - Dec 2018

Kreativ-kraft, Linköping, Sweden

- Got the internship by my own initiative
- Managed marketing tools and implemented plan for SEO
- Created content to websites, took photos and wrote texts

# **Education**

#### **Bachelor in Cognitive Science**

Aug 2018 - Jun 2021

Linköping University, Sweden

- Studying my second year of bachelor in Cognitive Science
- Studied courses in psychology, human behaviour and programming

# Organizational experience

## **Welcome Period- and Activity Committee Coordinator**

May 2019 - May 2020

ESN Linköping, Linköping University

- Organizing events for over 500 new exchange students
- Managed planning and marketing over 30 events so far
- Increased the number of participants at our events
- Established relationships with different associations at campus
- Motivate my committee to work hard while enjoying

## **Head of Marketing**

Jun 2018 - Jun 2019

Linköping Vegan Association, Linköping University

- Was incharge for all the marketing on different social media channels as Facebook and Instagram
- Designed and implemented a whole new website (<u>www.livaliu.se</u>)
- Increased the followers on Facebook with 40 %